Why not find a fast courier
to deliver the book?
You have connections to the Moon?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
You're too busy
to deal with such trivial matters.
I...
I also like Mr. Cheng's poetry.
I know his wife is a courier.
So,
why bother going so far?
The escort team is already at hand.
That's right.
Then let her go.
No.
From the Yun State to the Langyue State,
there will be many bandits on the way.
It's not worth risking my wife's life
for these few books
of mine.
You have a point.
Your wife's life is also important.
Then let's trade.
It's not a big deal.
Since it's what the princess wants,
as long as she can enter the Langyue,
I'll keep her safe.
Good.
Guards,
take all the wine to the general's mansion.
I always tell my father
that you are the most loyal eagle of Langyue.
This cup, I toast to you.
Mr. Cheng,
I admire your talent.
Can we meet in private?
I have no grudges against you.
Why do you want to hurt the agency?
When did I hurt the agency?
You sent a fake escort before.
And now you're talking about going to Langyue.
Are you planning another ambush
to make the agency the only escort agency?
Mr. Su,
You've got me wrong.
Actually, last time,
you were my escort.
I...
Look.
The escort route from Yunjing to Langyue
is very dangerous.
If you don't have enough strength
to reach Klak City safely,
how can you
travel between Yunjing and Langyue in the future?
You work for the Princess.
You can rest assured to take the escort.
Our Princess
seems to be arrogant and domineering,
but she cares about the people of Langyue.
She has been biding her time,
waiting for the right moment.
Now you are her chance.
Goodbye.
Why did you drink so much last night?
To numb yourself?
Why didn't you let me kill Yikeba?
My father trusted him so much.
But he not only framed my father for treason,
but also killed my whole family.
But with your current ability,
can you kill him?
Even if you succeed in a sneak attack,
the gate is heavily guarded.
Do you have a way to escape?
Even if it takes a life to exchange for a life,
I must kill him.
I said if you want revenge,
I'll help you.
But
you're always staring at Su Yuejiao.
I'm not happy about that.
When Yikeba was chasing me,
if it weren't for Su Yuejiao's mother,
I would have been dead.
I owe the Su family a life.
Repaying a favor or taking revenge,
you can only choose one.
I want to see her.
Then you have to hurry up.
She's going back to Yunjing today.
Before I change my mind.
Why are you here?
Where's the princess?
Can we talk alone?
What's the point?
Haven't you done enough damage to the Escort Agency?
You don't still like My Lord, do you?
You want to come back to the Agency with us?
I have to
tell you something.
Let's talk somewhere else.
Go ahead.
Do you want me to help you escape?
Are you willing to go back to Langyue with me?
You want to go back to Langyue?
Isn't that walking into a trap?
Yiguna is the princess of Langyue.
My Lord, why don't you stop her?
What if she really goes to Langyue?
She won't give up her escort agency.
Bai Yanli is naive
and stupid.
If she would refuse,
what are we here for?
Just in case.
You're afraid.
Then why did you let him go?
If you don't let him go through this,
how can he give up?
It makes sense,
but not much.
I'm the only son of a general of Langyue.
Back then,
my father was killed by the deputy general.
Your mother saved me.
To avoid being killed,
I had to wander in the Yun State,
hiding here and there.
I always wanted to go back to Langyue.
Only when I was a brigand,
I could get close to Langyue without being suspected.
Over time,
I became famous.
I didn't expect
you have such a background.
Actually,
I always felt sorry for my mother.
She was always hunted for saving you.
But
you were a villain.
I went to the agency not just to repay your kindness.
I met you
in Ning'an
and fell in love with you.
I thought
if you were willing to be with me,
I wouldn't go back.
Wait.
I escorted goods to Ning'an.
Ning'an?
I've been to Ning'an.
I know you're married,
and I'm very upset.
Then I learned
it's just a fake marriage,
I thought I had a chance.
Fake marriage?
It's a long story, Your Highness.
But I fell in love with my wife
at first sight.
But...
But you made it real.
I don't remember anything.
Yes.
I know you lost your memory.
I'm even a little happy.
Cheng Qi will only hurt you.
I won't.
I really like you.
I can't stand it anymore.
Don't, don't, don't.
Don't be impulsive, don't be impulsive, Princess.
Don't be impulsive, don't be impulsive.
Princess, listen to me.
Last time when he talked to Jiao,
I interrupted them.
This time,
let me hear how Jiao answers.
Are you willing to be with me?
No.
Are you still thinking about Cheng Qi?
Bai Yanli,
no matter how much I remember,
right now, the agency is all that matters.
There are people I need to protect.
Nothing can change my mind.
As expected,
I'm late for everything
now.
Bai,
I believe you have
more important things to do.
I'm going back to Langyue
to restore my father's reputation
and fulfill his wish
and open up the trade route.
Once the trade is established,
I'll have General Bai on my side.
This is what my mother left me.
It bears the emblem of my family.
Take it.
When you escort goods to the border,
my men
and the wolf warriors
will see it as seeing me.
They'll help you.
Then this time,
I won't hold back.
I was supposed to give it to you at Yun Bridge.
But...
Yun Bridge?
What about the words you said at Yun Bridge?
I've held a wedding ceremony with you,
and we've shared a wedding night.
You are my wife.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Who shared a wedding night with you?
We've had a wedding ceremony
and a wedding feast
in Ning'an.
Jiao,
I'll marry no one but you.
I'm sticking with you.
Those are just empty words to please a woman.
I've said them to everyone in the pleasure quarters.
Between us,
there's only falsehood left.
We were never meant to be together.
Now I'm the head of Xingyun.
Who would want to
fall back into the mud?
Go to the escort agency,
and be a live-in son-in-law?
Cheng Qi.
I know you're upset.
If you want to cry,
I'm here for you.
No need.
You still want to go with her, don't you?
I won't go.
You came to me first.
Tell me.
What do you want?
I want revenge.
Help me.
If we are a family,
I will definitely help you.
I haven't forgotten her.
I know.
Then why are you still willing to...
You'll be mine anyway.
But
what if Su Yuejiao accepts you?
Stay by her side.
Miss Su
I don't take escort missions.
Please behave yourself, Mr. Cheng.
Don't take escort missions?
When did the agency have such a rule?
Now it has.
Mr. Cheng, you'd better find another way.
Miss Su
Look,
the road back is long and dangerous.
I'm a weak scholar.
If I go back,
I'll be in great danger.
Are you going to
just stand by and watch?
You know our agency well.
Of course.
The agency is
the best in the city.
And a popular writer like me
needs your protection.
Thank you for your trust.
Then I...
The rule is newly made.
We don't take personal escort.
Please go.
Don't worry,
I'll leave for Yunjing today.
I don't want you to go.
I don't care.
You took my business,
you should be responsible for my goods.
Take him back to Yunjing.
Princess,
I'll be responsible for the scripts,
but what does it have to do
with Mr. Cheng?
How can he write without going back?
And they like to procrastinate.
You have to keep an eye on him
to make him submit on time.
I can't control him.
I...
I'll listen to you.
Why are you so frivolous?
Your Highness, we have rules.
We don't take personal escort
or send people.
Then don't treat him as a person.
Treat him as a thing.
Of course.
He's not a thing either.
Anyway, just get him safely back to Yunjing.
I'll pay double the fee.
Let's go.
Go back to Yunjing.
Ling Feng.
The new script you've presented
is different from the previous one.
Your Majesty, you have a keen eye.
This time,
the performance is to pray for peace.
So,
I made some changes.
Then tell me,
why the previous one was not suitable?
I still want to know
what happened to Ning Anzhi.
Your Majesty,
I...
What?
Can't remember?
Or don't remember at all?
Your Majesty, forgive me.
I...
Guards!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Ling Feng, for your misconduct,
take 20 lashes!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
I am guilty and deserve punishment.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
It's all due to the poor discipline of the Ling family,
that such a fool was raised.
Grand Preceptor,
what crime do you have?
Ling Feng's actions
must be the result of someone else writing for him.
I failed in my oversight,
and should be punished accordingly.
So, in your opinion,
how should I punish you?
I have also reviewed Ling Feng's writings.
I believed his words
and thought that since he's from the Ministry of Rites,
he must be reliable.
I didn't realize I misjudged him.
I request to resign from the Ministry of Civil Office.
I hope Your Majesty
won't take it out on the two young men.
Your Majesty,
I believe
that for the sake of the years of diligent service
of the Grand Preceptor to the court,
for his years of service.
What about the oratorical contest?
What are you going to do?
I'm willing to make amends.
I'll find Cheng Qi
and hold the contest together
to ensure everything goes smoothly.
You may leave.
If anything goes wrong again,
I won't let you off the hook.
Yes, sir.
Your Majesty.
Cheng Qi is back.
When will the mission of Princess Langyue
arrive?
The secret report from Langyue
should be in a month.
Yigu Na seems to be capricious,
but she is actually shrewd,
and is favored by the King of Langyue.
She has been raised in Klak City for so many years.
to express
our sincerity in bilateral trade.
Secondly,
we want to leverage the strength of Yun State
to dig out the big fish inside.
He is waiting.
So am I.
Cheng Qi's acquaintance with her
may also be your idea.
Keep an eye on
the speech contest.
You must kill two birds with one stone.
Yes.
You can ask anyone,
but why did you ask Cheng Qi to write for Ling Feng?
Now the Emperor is blaming,
and even father is involved.
Are you doing this on purpose?
Brother, don't blame.
If it weren't for Cheng Qi,
the poetry of others
would never have caught the Emperor's eye.
That's just an excuse.
You think I don't know
you just want to keep Cheng Qi at home,
so you made up these reasons.
You, a woman,
how can you do such shameless things?
How dare you say it's for the family?
You're really shameless.
If you take the lead,
what if something goes wrong,
who will take the blame for you?
How dare you disobey my order!
I warned Ling Feng not to do it,
but my brother insisted on
reporting Ling Feng to the emperor.
Dad.
Look at her now.
How dare you talk back!
I'll teach you a lesson for dad.
My Lord.
Qijia.
Dad.
I know I can't compare with my brother,
so just kill me.
If you want to die, go far away.
Shut up!
Dad
I'll give you the list and account books
of shops,
money,
and other properties.
Please forgive me.
and let me
go back to my mother's hometown to reflect.
From today on,
you can only reflect in the mansion.
Don't think about going anywhere.
Get out.
Yes.
Dad.
Just let her off like this?
What else do you want?
You were the one who was careless.
Don't blame others.
She's been managing
the Zhang family business for years.
Move the money as soon as possible.
You and I
should make a thorough plan.
Yes.
Grandpa.
We're back.
My Lord.
Gong Xi.
Facha.
Grandpa.
Grandpa is back.
Mengxin.
You big dummy.
Are you okay?
Feifei.
Have you been eating well?
I miss you so much.
It's good to see you're fine.
I miss you too.
Good, good.
It's good to see you're fine.
Xin, look,
I bought you earrings in Klak City.
Look.
Mine?
Do you like them?
Yes, it's beautiful.
You've lost weight.
Zhen, Lingyu.
Jiaojiao, take care.
Take care.
You little rascal,
if you ever make such a rash decision again,
I'll break your legs.
I know.
Uncle,
I picked these for a long time.
Those are gifts for you.
Please help me give them away.
Did you miss me?
I knew you would like it.
Why is he here?
What's going on?
Did they make up?
No.
Jiaojiao was injured and unconscious.
She forgot about Cheng Qi.
She forgot?
Well,
my Lord was injured in the robbery.
Then,
he forgot about his son-in-law.
That's good.
My mission is to take you back to Yunjing.
Now that we're here, you can go.
Okay, I'm going home.
You...
Look, this is the Su's house.
Please leave.
You heartless man.
I supported you so much before.
The Escort Agency doesn't welcome you.
You should go.
My son-in-law.
You go to the Yue Lao Pavilion first.
Okay.
Mom, I went to the City of Klara.
And I made a new friend.
My daughter is so brave.
But you can't
do anything so dangerous anymore.
It will make us worried.
No.
Mom.
Now I finally understand that
the head of the family is not just a title,
not just a responsibility,
but also requires courage, strategy,
and careful consideration.
Now there is a chance.
I want to open a branch in Langyue.
You've grown up.
I believe in you.
Grandpa, this city is so beautiful.
There's a building over there,
which looks exactly like the Huayue Tower.
Eat.
Jiaojiao, eat more meat.
You're getting thinner.
Grandpa,
her bowl is almost full.
Besides,
we are in the Klak City,
and Princess is taking care of us.
We have a good life.
Yes, grandpa.
I'm doing well.
I'm sorry for causing trouble
for the Escort Agency.
You are apologizing.
It seems that you really suffered.
The most urgent task now
is to restore the reputation and business of the Escort Agency.
Although we have taken on a new escort,
it can't solve the problem at hand.
We have to start from scratch.
My lord, what do you want to do?
We'll listen to you.
From tomorrow,
whether it's guarding a house
or being a bodyguard for a shop,
we'll do all the trivial and hard work
in the city of Yunjing.
That's not right.
I'll go find
some old clients.
It's better than doing chores.
I won a lot of money playing cards.
Jiaojiao, you can use it first.
I can also make handicrafts
to exchange for money.
Jiaojiao,
believe in my face,
You should believe in my luck.
You should believe in my brother's skill.
Then you should believe in my
appetite.
The point now is not lack of money,
but to restore the reputation of the Escort Agency.
Let everyone know that we are reliable,
not a black shop that steals goods.
My Lord.
Come with me.
Leave a piece of rib.
Well,
it is said that
there are many rich men's in-laws,
but rarely
armoury agency in-laws.
To know the way of survival of the agency,
just listen to me.
Good.
It is said that the Su's Agency in Yunjing
is famous for its motto: "I'll protect the goods until I die".
The young female head
is upright and forthright.
But in order to protect her own escort order,
she fell into the trap of the cunning scholar.
The scholar
fell in love at first sight
when he first saw the female head.
By some strange coincidence, he set a trap
to trick the female head into marrying him.
The scholar lied and set up a trap for the female head.
If the two of them can really end up together,
it's a good thing.
Good thing?
Have you asked her opinion?
He is a playboy who deceives women.
That's it.
Gong Xi
What's going on?
My lord, he's reading the storybook.
He said you like it.
I don't know him.
Don't let him make trouble in front of the escort agency.
I told you before.
My Lord lost his memory.
He doesn't remember Cheng Qi.
How dare he call himself my son-in-law?
Watch out for a beating.
The book "The Daily Life of the Men-in-law in the Escort Agency"
is only two pence now.
Two pence?
Good.
You can change a place to sell it.
No.
The rent of the escort agency...
Grandpa.
I paid it.
It's quite a lot.
You have to pay compensation for breach of contract.
Is my family so poor?
Didn't you say the escort agency needs to gather people?
This guy can gather people,
and can also pay us money.
How good!
Well.
You
should move over there.
In case Jiaojiao sees it
and wants to listen.
Okay.
Gong Xi, Fai Cai.
How can we let the guests stand and listen to the book?
Go get some low stools.
And some tea and snacks.
My Lord.
If you need anything, just tell us.
You can order at any time.
Good, good, good.
I said the divorce was fake, right?
Didn't she just drive him away?
I guess they quarreled.
Quarrel in bed, make up in bed.
Yes, yes, yes.
Tell me the truth.
Do you really not remember Cheng Qi?
I didn't remember before.
But now you remember.
And then?
I got hurt on the head in the City of Klak.
It took me a while to remember people and things.
Everyone always talks about him in front of me.
So I remember.
Then why do you pretend not to remember?
I don't want to go back to the past.
It's good to treat him as a stranger.
You really don't plan to forgive him?
I don't have much ground
to say forgive or not forgive.
I just want to focus on the Escort Agency.
Right.
The Escort Agency is the most important.
Otherwise, where will I live in the future?
Don't worry. I can't let you suffer.
But he's telling stories at the door of the Escort Agency now,
which has brought some popularity back to the Agency.
Did you forget how he hurt you at that time?
Jiaojiao, if you don't want to accept him,
I'll help you get rid of him.
I heard that
the best way to forget someone
is to find a new person to replace him.
Leave it to me.
No.
I don't want to get into a worse situation.
Let me run the Escort Agency well first.
It's mine.
Miss
You have placed orders for three days in a row.
Let me take the stool home for you.
I appreciate your trust in the Escort Agency,
but can I ask why?
If we take 15 orders a day,
no matter how big or small,
we can ask Mr. Cheng to tell a new chapter.
So I'm counting on you.
It was very dangerous.
Gong Xi
You go tell Mr. Cheng later
that two new chapters will be told for the employer today.
My treat.
My Lord, can we go too?
No, we should go escort.
Be careful.
The phoenix coronet and robes.
My Lord wants to invite you to the Yue Lao Pavilion.